Everything is for Allah,
in your Deen, in your
religion,
in your worship, in your
devotion.
Everything is for Allah,
in your worldly life.
Everything is for Allah too,
So, you can now say,
are you also saying that,
when I transact business,
it should be for Allah?
Yes.
How?
The rules in your business
transactions,
must be in line with the
instructions
of the Sharia.
Whatever Allah has
prohibited,
you must not do.
...
Can we hear me,
Ikhoa?
So, in the matters of your
business
transactions, Allah has
prohibited rebar.
So, if you avoid rebar,
and very many other business
transactions,
that the Sharia has
prohibited,
by that, your worldly life
regarding your
business,
would be for the sake of
Allah.
Why?
Because you have employed the
restrictions,
and the limitations of the
Sharia in
it.
So, it becomes deen for you,
it becomes worship for you.